

export const mathsOneToTen = [
    {
        theWord : 'stingy',
        question: `Michael is but his brother is ..................`,
        options: [{
            a: 'prudence',
            b: 'attentiveness',
            c: 'diligence',
            d: 'sharpness'
        }],
        answer: '4'
    },

      {
        question: 'What is the name of your village?',
        options: [{
            a: 'shanga',
            b: 'wara',
            c: 'kware',
            d: 'tambuwal'
        }],
        answer: 'wara'
    },

        {
        question: 'How old is the first man made car?',
        options: [{
            a: '52',
            b: '37',
            c: '79',
            d: '87'
        }],
        answer: '87'
    },
      {
        question: 'What is the most expensive car company in the world?',
        options: [{
            a: 'toyota',
            b: 'tesla',
            c: 'bugatti',
            d: 'honda'
        }],
        answer: 'toyota'
    }
]

export const mathsElevenToTwenty = [
    {
        theWord : 'stingy',
        question: `Michael is but his brother is ..................`,
        options: [{
            a: 'prudence',
            b: 'attentiveness',
            c: 'diligence',
            d: 'sharpness'
        }],
        answer: '4'
    },

      {
        question: 'What is the name of your village?',
        options: [{
            a: 'shanga',
            b: 'wara',
            c: 'kware',
            d: 'tambuwal'
        }],
        answer: 'wara'
    },

        {
        question: 'How old is the first man made car?',
        options: [{
            a: '52',
            b: '37',
            c: '79',
            d: '87'
        }],
        answer: '87'
    },
      {
        question: 'What is the most expensive car company in the world?',
        options: [{
            a: 'toyota',
            b: 'tesla',
            c: 'bugatti',
            d: 'honda'
        }],
        answer: 'toyota'
    }
]


export const mathsTwentyOneToThirty = [
    {
        theWord : 'stingy',
        question: `Michael is but his brother is ..................`,
        options: [{
            a: 'prudence',
            b: 'attentiveness',
            c: 'diligence',
            d: 'sharpness'
        }],
        answer: '4'
    },

      {
        question: 'What is the name of your village?',
        options: [{
            a: 'shanga',
            b: 'wara',
            c: 'kware',
            d: 'tambuwal'
        }],
        answer: 'wara'
    },

        {
        question: 'How old is the first man made car?',
        options: [{
            a: '52',
            b: '37',
            c: '79',
            d: '87'
        }],
        answer: '87'
    },
      {
        question: 'What is the most expensive car company in the world?',
        options: [{
            a: 'toyota',
            b: 'tesla',
            c: 'bugatti',
            d: 'honda'
        }],
        answer: 'toyota'
    }
]


export const mathsThirtyOneToForty = [
    {
        theWord : 'stingy',
        question: `Michael is but his brother is ..................`,
        options: [{
            a: 'prudence',
            b: 'attentiveness',
            c: 'diligence',
            d: 'sharpness'
        }],
        answer: '4'
    },

      {
        question: 'What is the name of your village?',
        options: [{
            a: 'shanga',
            b: 'wara',
            c: 'kware',
            d: 'tambuwal'
        }],
        answer: 'wara'
    },

        {
        question: 'How old is the first man made car?',
        options: [{
            a: '52',
            b: '37',
            c: '79',
            d: '87'
        }],
        answer: '87'
    },
      {
        question: 'What is the most expensive car company in the world?',
        options: [{
            a: 'toyota',
            b: 'tesla',
            c: 'bugatti',
            d: 'honda'
        }],
        answer: 'toyota'
    }
]